mindri.com 2013-05-03

# הצהרת פרטיות - Mindri

1. General  

1.1. Mindri Ltd ("We" or the "Company") Operate www.Mindri.co.il website (the "Site"). Our Company respects the privacy of its users ("You" or the "End User") and this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") shall apply to any use of this Site or any of our services (the "Services"). 

1.2.    If You choose to use Our Site or any of Our Services, You will be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy and therefor if You do not agree to be bound by any of its terms provided herein do not use our Site or any of Our Services.

1.3.  The terms of Our Privacy Policy specified herein are part of Our terms of use, which may be viewed at http://www.mindri.co.il/term_of_use ("Terms of Use"). By viewing the content of Our Site, You undertake to act in accordance to Our Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy.

2. Data Collection   
  
2.1  We collect certain information concerning Your web usage and websites You have visited. Among others, we may collect information concerning the web pages You have viewed and Your activity in those pages as well as impressions, clicks, search terms and external links used by You. Furthermore, we may collect information regarding Your IP address, the duration of Your stay in other web sites and Your activity in those sites. All information collected by Us shall be kept according to the terms provided herein. 

2.2 Other information We may collect, is information You submit while using our Services. Such information may include Your name, date of birth, gender, phone number, e-mail address etc. 

2.3  End Users are required to fill in Some of the information we collect when registering for our Services. In some cases End User shall be required to submit this information as a condition for the provision of Our Services ("Mandatory Information"). Mandatory Information is marked as such and it is hereby clarified that the submission this information though not compulsory is a preliminary condition for the provision of any of Our Services or the use of Our Site.

2.4  The use We make of information collected by Us will be in accordance with this Privacy Policy and any applicable law. Note that the information We gather is mostly statistic and is not of personal nature. The information we collect is used among others for the improvement of the Services We provide. 

2.5  We reserves the right to address You occasionally via e-mail, SMS text massages, or any other means of communication, in order to provide You with information concerning events we think may interest You, additional services We provide and other marketing information We wish to deliver You. In case You desire not to receive any of this information please contact Us and ask for Your removal from our distribution list.

2.6 We reserve the right to transfer some of the information we collect to certain third parties in which help Us analyze and improve Our Services. In any event information We transfer to other parties shall continue to be subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

3.  Information You Disclose To Third Parties 

3.1.  Part of the services offered on our Site may be provided, managed, owned or controlled by third parties ("Third Parties"). For example, the payment and defrayment for Services We provide is made by PayPal Inc., using its own computers and clearing method. Third Parties may gather information concerning End Users using their services independently and the use of such information is subject to such Third Party's privacy policies. Therefor You are advised to read these privacy policies prior to the use of any Third Party services.

3.2. It is hereby clarified that We will not, under any circumstances, be liable for any direct or indirect damages relating the use of Third Party's services including damages relating the reliance on any information made available by such Third Parties.

Without derogating from the aforementioned We reserve the right to disclose any and all End User information we have in the following events: 

3.2.1. In order to ensure the proper operation of Our Site and Services. 

3.2.2. In case that according to Our sole discretion any violation, breach or misuse of Our Site or Services is made. 

3.2.3. In case that according to Our sole discretion a felony (as provided under Israeli law) is made using Our site.

3.2.4. In case that We are required by any governmental authority to disclose any of the information We hold.

3.2.5. In case of a dispute or legal proceedings between You and Us, or any of our legal representatives.

3.2.6. In case We believe that it is necessary to transfer the information We have in order to prevent the infliction of any bodily or mental damage upon any End User or other individual.

3.3. We reserve the right to transfer the information We gather, according to Our sole discretion, to a subsidiary or affiliate, for as long as such subsidiary or affiliate comply with the terms of this Privacy Policy. In case of a merger between Us and any third party, We reserve the right to transfer information We have gathered to the newly formed entity for as long as such entity also undertakes to comply with the terms provided herein.

4. Information Security  
4.1 We take reasonable measures in order to keep Our Site and Services secured from any unauthorized breach. However, despite these measures We take We cannot assure that no unauthorized breach will take place on our Site or databases. By using Our Site and Services You acknowledge that You are aware that Our Site Services and databases may be vulnerable to such an unauthorized breach and You hereby release Us from any liability relating Our Site, Services and databases security.

5. Right to Peruse InformationUnder the Israeli Protection of Privacy Law, 5741-1981, every individual is entitled, whether himself or by a proxy so authorized in writing or through his/her legal guardian, to peruse information pertaining to himself/herself that is stored in a database. Having perused such information and found it to be inaccurate, incomplete, unclear or out of date, such person may contact the database owner and request it to correct, amend or delete the data in question. Had the database owner refused to permit access or comply with a request to amend or delete information, the individual who applied for such amendment or delete may appeal to the magistrate’s court as stipulated in the applicable regulations.

Moreover, should information contained in Our database be used for purposes of personally soliciting You, based on Your affiliation to any population group as determined according to one or more attributes of people whose names are included in the database (“solicitation for commercial purposes”), the Protection of Privacy Law, 5741-1981, entitles You to submit a written request that such information pertaining to You be deleted from the database. In such a case, the Site management will delete any information required for solicitation for commercial purposes as stated above. Please note that deleting such information might prevent You from continuing to receive services from the website. Any information required by the website management to conduct its business – including documentation of commercial and other activities performed by You on the website – will continue to be legally stored by the website management according to law, but will no longer be used to personally solicit You. If You do not receive notification that the information that the website management was requested to delete has in fact been deleted according to the provisions of this paragraph within 30 days, You will be entitled to apply to a magistrate’s court in the manner specified in the applicable regulations having the force of law, in order for it to instruct the website management to act as stated.

6. CookiesWe use cookies ("Cookies") and other tracking technologies, which are partly comprised of personal encrypted data sent to and extracted from Your computer. These tracking technologies are used in order to secure our database, gather statistic information and verify the entity of End User's approaching Our Site. 

6.1. Using these costume tracking technologies we may have Your computer store certain data concerning Your browser usage in files accessible to Us. Our access to this stored information makes Your use of Our Site and Services more efficient due to the fact that large portion of this stored information need not be recreated when you re-enter our Site. These tracking technologies also enables Us to collect and store information concerning services, search queries and external links you have used, as well as other web pages and advertisements You have viewed. We may also use cookies, and other technologies, in order to measure the effectiveness and to personalize our services.

6.2. Cookies   
We use are text files created by your browser according to a command sent from Our Site. Cookies contain a variety of information, such as the pages you have accessed, the amount of time you spent on the Sites, the source from which you reached the Site, sections and information you have sought during your entries into the Sites, and more. Cookies are also used to obviate the need to enter your personal details into the system on the occasion of every individual entry into Our Site. You may choose to delete the cookies from 

6.3. Your hard-drive by accessing the temporary internet files folder in Your control panel. Note that deleting these files may cause You not to be able to reuse Our Site or reuse it in the manner used prior to the deletion.

7. VariationsWe reserve the right to revise and amend this Privacy Policy from time to time without providing you with any prior notice and any revised version will be deemed to be applicable from the first date of publication on this Site.
